export const englishAssessmentTest = [
  {
    question: '1. We don\u2019t have ___________ money.',
    options: ['some', 'any', 'no'],
    correctAnswer: 'any',
  },
  {
    question: '2. My father\u2019s ____________.',
    options: ['dentist', 'a dentist', 'the dentist'],
    correctAnswer: 'a dentist',
  },
  {
    question: '3. Martin __________ in the gym.',
    options: ['doesn’t often go', 'doesn’t go often', 'often doesn’t go'],
    correctAnswer: 'doesn’t often go',
  },
  {
    question: '4. Can we meet __________ Monday evening?',
    options: ['at', 'in', 'on'],
    correctAnswer: 'on',
  },
  {
    question: '5. Jess ____________ French really well.',
    options: ['speak', 'speaks', 'to speak'],
    correctAnswer: 'speaks',
  },
  {
    question: '6. They ___________ dinner at the moment.',
    options: ['have', 'having', 'are having'],
    correctAnswer: 'are having',
  },
  {
    question: '7. A: \u201cCan I take your order?\u201d B: ____________',
    options: [
      'I’m having a steak, please.',
      'I’ll have a steak, please.',
      'I have a steak, please.',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'I’ll have a steak, please.',
  },
  {
    question: '8. This is ___________ holiday I\u2019ve ever had.',
    options: ['the best', 'most best', 'best'],
    correctAnswer: 'the best',
  },
  {
    question: '9. We ____________ shopping yesterday.',
    options: ['got', 'made', 'went'],
    correctAnswer: 'went',
  },
  {
    question: '10. The weather __________ so nice on Saturday.',
    options: ['didn’t be', 'wasn’t', 'weren’t'],
    correctAnswer: 'wasn’t',
  },
  {
    question: '11. We __________ a really good time at the festival.',
    options: ['spent', 'had', 'did'],
    correctAnswer: 'had',
  },
  {
    question: '12. That phone is ________ than mine.',
    options: ['most expensive', 'more expensive', 'expenciver'],
    correctAnswer: 'more expensive',
  },
  {
    question: '13. He\u2019s eaten _________ cakes, and now he feels ill.',
    options: ['too many', 'too much', 'too little'],
    correctAnswer: 'too many',
  },
  {
    question: '14. I don\u2019t have ________ free time these days.',
    options: ['no', 'some', 'any'],
    correctAnswer: 'any',
  },
  {
    question: '15. They ___________ to the cinema. They\u2019ll be back in an hour.',
    options: ['have been', 'have gone', 'have got'],
    correctAnswer: 'have gone',
  },
  {
    question: '16. James and Tina ________ married for 10 years. They got divorced last month.',
    options: ['were', 'been', 'got'],
    correctAnswer: 'were',
  },
  {
    question: '17. When I _______ up it __________.',
    options: ['Get/was snowing', 'was getting/was snowing', 'got/was snowing'],
    correctAnswer: 'got/was snowing',
  },
  {
    question: '18. You ___________ wear a uniform at work if you don\u2019t want to.',
    options: ['mustn’t', 'shouldn’t', 'don’t have to'],
    correctAnswer: 'don’t have to',
  },
  {
    question: '19. David __________ me he wanted to get a burger.',
    options: ['told', 'said', 'replied'],
    correctAnswer: 'told',
  },
  {
    question: '20. Is he looking __________ to the party?',
    options: ['after', 'for', 'forward'],
    correctAnswer: 'forward',
  },
  {
    question: '21. I don\u2019t mind people __________ with me.',
    options: ['to disagree', 'disagreeing', 'disagree'],
    correctAnswer: 'disagreeing',
  },
  {
    question: '22. Could you drive __________? I hate it when you drive fast.',
    options: ['slower', 'slowlyer', 'more slowly'],
    correctAnswer: 'more slowly',
  },
  {
    question: '23. ________ you call me when he arrives?',
    options: ['Shall', 'will', 'do'],
    correctAnswer: 'Will',
  },
  {
    question: '24. I have plenty of free time because I only work ________.',
    options: ['temporary', 'part-time', 'self-employed'],
    correctAnswer: 'part-time',
  },
  {
    question:
      '25. It was very ________ that Jeff drove past and saw us just after we\u2019d missed the bus.',
    options: ['fortune', 'fortunate', 'fortunately'],
    correctAnswer: 'fortunate',
  },
  {
    question: '26. When Tomas ______ home, the kids __________ because they __________ all day.',
    options: [
      'was getting/slept/had played',
      'got/were sleeping/played',
      'got/were sleeping/had played',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'got/were sleeping/had played',
  },
  {
    question: '27. Sally _________ her driving test if she doesn\u2019t practise more.',
    options: ['won’t pass', 'wouldn’t pass', 'doesn’t pass'],
    correctAnswer: 'won’t pass',
  },
  {
    question: '28. I would have told you about the concert if I __________ you were interested.',
    options: ['know', 'knew', 'had known'],
    correctAnswer: 'had known',
  },
  {
    question: '29. Richard told me he ____________ James at the party on Saturday.',
    options: ['saw', 'had seen', 'will see'],
    correctAnswer: 'had seen',
  },
  {
    question: '30. The Olympics and Paralympics ___________ in London in 2012.',
    options: ['were held', 'held', 'are held'],
    correctAnswer: 'were held',
  },
  {
    question: '31. ________ are becoming an increasingly large proportion of many societies.',
    options: ['Unemployed', 'The unemployed', 'The unemployed people'],
    correctAnswer: 'The unemployed',
  },
  {
    question: '32. We played the music quietly ________ wake the children.',
    options: ['to not', 'not to', 'so as not to'],
    correctAnswer: 'so as not to',
  },
  {
    question: '33. I love ________ in that shop.',
    options: ['a furniture', 'the furnitures', 'the furniture'],
    correctAnswer: 'the furniture',
  },
  {
    question: '34. Does anyone know where ________?',
    options: ['lives Petra', 'does Petra live', 'Petra lives'],
    correctAnswer: 'does Petra live',
  },
  {
    question: '35. ________ the very steep climb up the last hill, I really enjoyed the walk.',
    options: ['Although', 'In spite', 'Despite'],
    correctAnswer: 'Despite',
  },
  {
    question: '36. You have to take Diana\u2019s age into ________ when you judge her work.',
    options: ['place', 'account', 'care'],
    correctAnswer: 'account',
  },
  {
    question:
      '37. I\u2019m ________ and tired of listening to all your problems \u2013 do something about them!',
    options: ['fed up', 'sick', 'bored'],
    correctAnswer: 'fed up',
  },
  {
    question: '38. I find it ________ when apps keep updating themselves all the time.',
    options: ['confused', 'confusion', 'confusing'],
    correctAnswer: 'confusing',
  },
  {
    question:
      '39. I\u2019m sure you wish you ________ (not buy) that car. It\u2019s been nothing but trouble.',
    options: ['Hadn’t bought', 'didn’t buy', 'don’t buy'],
    correctAnswer: 'Hadn’t bought',
  },
  {
    question: '40. By the end of July I _____________ my painting course.',
    options: ['will be finishing', 'will finish', 'will have finished'],
    correctAnswer: 'will have finished',
  },
  {
    question:
      '41. We\u2019re ________ find a petrol station soon. We\u2019ve been driving for three hours.',
    options: ['sure', 'must', 'bound to'],
    correctAnswer: 'bound to',
  },
  {
    question:
      '42. Not until I\u2019ve saved enough money ________ leave home and try to find my own flat.',
    options: ['I will', 'will I', 'I’ll'],
    correctAnswer: 'will I',
  },
  {
    question: '43. Could you wash these ________ cups, please?',
    options: ['coffee’s', 'coffee', 'coffee of'],
    correctAnswer: 'coffee',
  },
  {
    question:
      '44. The villagers ________ have left the area because they had difficulty growing food.',
    options: ['are thought', 'may', 'understood to'],
    correctAnswer: 'may',
  },
  {
    question: '45. It looks ________ Myron has finally learned to play the violin.',
    options: ['as if', 'that', 'though'],
    correctAnswer: 'as if',
  },
  {
    question:
      '46. We would rather ________ on holiday in August, but we had to wait until September.',
    options: ['our', 'have gone', 'that we go'],
    correctAnswer: 'have gone',
  },
  {
    question:
      '47. Working as a dog groomer might not pay that well, but it\u2019s a very _________ job.',
    options: ['unpaid', 'contract', 'rewarding'],
    correctAnswer: 'rewarding',
  },
  {
    question: '48. If it was ________ to me, I\u2019d go on holiday to Sicily twice a year.',
    options: ['go', 'up', 'prefer'],
    correctAnswer: 'up',
  },
  {
    question: '49. What\u2019s the name of Stuart\u2019s wife? It on the tip of my ________.',
    options: ['tongue', 'heart', 'head'],
    correctAnswer: 'tongue',
  },
  {
    question:
      '50. I\u2019ve lost my job, so for a few months we\u2019ll have to get ________ on my wife\u2019s salary.',
    options: ['by', 'back', 'with'],
    correctAnswer: 'by',
  },
]
